Her love is [music]
in your head. You lost your earrings in
her bed. You couldn't tell her that you
lost her cuz you're scared [music]
and you're not [singing] talking. So,
you think of what to say and save it
[music] for
another
>> [singing]
>> day cuz you just never had the heart.
[music] Now, they just drift
>> [singing]
>> apart
from you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Her love
is in your head. [music] You lost your
earrings in
her bed. You couldn't [singing] tell her
that you lost her cuz you're scared and
you're not [music] talking. [singing]
So, you think of what to say and save it
for
another
day cuz [music] you just never had the
heart. Now, they just drift
apart [music and singing]
from you.
>> Extra, extra, read all about it.
Magazines, feelings, and you can't get
out [music] of it. Extra, [singing]
extra, read all about it. Magazines,
feelings, and you can't get out of it.
Extra, extra, [music] read all about it.
Magazines, feelings, and you can't get
out of it. Extra, extra, [music] read
all about it. Magazines, feelings, and
you get get out of it.
>> [music]
>> Extra, extra me,
all about [music]
it. Back is in his feelings, can't get
get out of it. Extra, extra [singing]
me, all about it. Back is in his
feelings, can't get [music] get out of
it. Can't get out of it. [singing] Can't
get out of it.
>> Okay, well, I hope you like my mixtape.